{
    "subject": "resource/Living_My_Life_(song)",
    "predicate": "ontology/producer",
    "object": "resource/Alex_Sadkin",
    "human_readable": "The producer of 'Living My Life' song is Alex Sadkin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9264412522315979,
            "question": "Which artist might have collaborated with Alex Sadkin on 'Living My Life'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9249972701072693,
            "question": "What is the title of the song produced by Alex Sadkin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9218626618385315,
            "question": "Alex Sadkin is known for producing which song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8954678773880005,
            "question": "Is Alex Sadkin involved in music production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8709433674812317,
            "question": "What song features the production work of Alex Sadkin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.865310549736023,
            "question": "Who produced the song 'Living My Life'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8620497584342957,
            "question": "Can you name a song produced by Alex Sadkin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7398009896278381,
            "question": "What is the name of the producer of 'Living My Life'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6210525631904602,
            "question": "Who created the music for 'Living My Life'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39665061235427856,
            "question": "Alex Sadkin's work includes which musical piece?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The producer of 'Living My Life' song is Alex Sadkin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2961_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who created the music for 'Living My Life'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2961_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the producer of 'Living My Life'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2961_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a song produced by Alex Sadkin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2961_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2961_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2961_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2961_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2961_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2961_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2961_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2961_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2961_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2961_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2961_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Alex Sadkin produced Grace Jones\u2019 album \"Living My Life\" (1982), which includes the song \"Living My Life.\" Therefore, the statement that Alex Sadkin is the producer of 'Living My Life' song is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}